{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","address":"1980 Bagley","zipcode":"48216","owner":"Valley Services, Inc.","licenseNumber":"047837","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/7/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000603477698DC454C0A85EB2BCEE294540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44558","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","inspectionDate":"2018-12-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"3","pfcount":"3","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"6","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"6","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-02-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"at toilet in restroom men's","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Food","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-202.15","violationDescription":"FOOD packages shall be in good condition and protect the integrity of the contents so that the FOOD is not exposed to ADULTERATION or potential contaminants. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food package(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dented, dented on seam or swollen","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-501.112","violationDescription":"Dead or trapped birds, insects, rodents, and other pests shall be removed from control devices and the PREMISES at a frequency that prevents their accumulation,  decomposition, or the attraction of pests.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dead/trapped pest(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."},{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\r\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \r\n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\r\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\r\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 70 degrees f to 41 degrees F for more than 4 hours","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"44558","inspectionDate":"12/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."}]},{"inspectionid":"43597","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","inspectionDate":"2018-10-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43597","inspectionDate":"10/1/2018","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DELIVERY AREA","subLocation":"Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"43597","inspectionDate":"10/1/2018","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"4-301.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT for cooling and heating FOOD, and holding cold and hot FOOD, shall be sufficient in number and capacity to provide FOOD temperatures as required. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide additional equipment to meet requirement above."},{"inspectionid":"43597","inspectionDate":"10/1/2018","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"DELIVERY AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"}]},{"inspectionid":"42078","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","inspectionDate":"2018-05-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42078","inspectionDate":"5/2/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Toilet room door(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Propped open","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the Self-closing device","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Do not prop door open."},{"inspectionid":"42078","inspectionDate":"5/2/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In prep area","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."}]},{"inspectionid":"44212","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","inspectionDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"3","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44212","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelf","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"44212","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Paper toweling","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"44212","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-301.13","violationDescription":"A sink used for FOOD preparation or UTENSIL washing, or a service sink or curbed cleaning facility used for the disposal of mop water or similar wastes, may not be provided with the handwashing aids and devices required for a HANDWASHING SINK as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Soap and towel(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Provided at","subProblem":"Mop sink","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"At the Mop sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove soap/paper towels from mop sink."},{"inspectionid":"44212","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Milk","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"44212","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\r\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \r\n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\r\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\r\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 70 degrees f to 41 degrees F for more than 4 hours","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Speed rack","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"44212","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"38660","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","inspectionDate":"2017-04-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"3","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38660","inspectionDate":"4/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Paper toweling","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"38660","inspectionDate":"4/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Milk","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"38660","inspectionDate":"4/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\r\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \r\n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\r\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\r\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 70 degrees f to 41 degrees F for more than 4 hours","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Speed rack","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"38660","inspectionDate":"4/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"38660","inspectionDate":"4/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-301.13","violationDescription":"A sink used for FOOD preparation or UTENSIL washing, or a service sink or curbed cleaning facility used for the disposal of mop water or similar wastes, may not be provided with the handwashing aids and devices required for a HANDWASHING SINK as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Soap and towel(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Provided at","subProblem":"Mop sink","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"At the Mop sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove soap/paper towels from mop sink."},{"inspectionid":"38660","inspectionDate":"4/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelf","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."}]},{"inspectionid":"37087","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","inspectionDate":"2016-11-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37087","inspectionDate":"11/10/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"37087","inspectionDate":"11/10/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2656","name":"Valley Foods","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored with food-contact portion exposed","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"At the Single service items","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store inverted."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2656"}}